import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const hiragana: Question[] = [
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ka"?', options: ['か', 'き', 'こ', 'く'], correctAnswer: 'か' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "shi"?', options: ['し', 'ち', 'さ', 'す'], correctAnswer: 'し' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ta"?', options: ['た', 'ち', 'て', 'と'], correctAnswer: 'た' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "mo"?', options: ['も', 'み', 'ま', 'め'], correctAnswer: 'も' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "yu"?', options: ['ゆ', 'や', 'よ', 'え'], correctAnswer: 'ゆ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "a"?', options: ['あ', 'う', 'え', 'い'], correctAnswer: 'あ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "i"?', options: ['い', 'え', 'あ', 'お'], correctAnswer: 'い' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "u"?', options: ['う', 'あ', 'お', 'え'], correctAnswer: 'う' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "e"?', options: ['え', 'あ', 'お', 'う'], correctAnswer: 'え' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "o"?', options: ['お', 'え', 'い', 'あ'], correctAnswer: 'お' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ki"?', options: ['き', 'け', 'く', 'こ'], correctAnswer: 'き' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ku"?', options: ['け', 'く', 'こ', 'き'], correctAnswer: 'く' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ke"?', options: ['か', 'け', 'く', 'こ'], correctAnswer: 'け' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ko"?', options: ['け', 'こ', 'く', 'か'], correctAnswer: 'こ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "sa"?', options: ['せ', 'し', 'す', 'さ'], correctAnswer: 'さ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "su"?', options: ['せ', 'す', 'し', 'さ'], correctAnswer: 'す' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "se"?', options: ['す', 'せ', 'さ', 'し'], correctAnswer: 'せ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "so"?', options: ['し', 'そ', 'す', 'さ'], correctAnswer: 'そ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "chi"?', options: ['ち', 'し', 'つ', 'て'], correctAnswer: 'ち' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "tsu"?', options: ['つ', 'ち', 'て', 'と'], correctAnswer: 'つ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "te"?', options: ['て', 'た', 'と', 'ち'], correctAnswer: 'て' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "to"?', options: ['と', 'た', 'て', 'つ'], correctAnswer: 'と' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "na"?', options: ['な', 'に', 'ぬ', 'ね'], correctAnswer: 'な' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ni"?', options: ['ぬ', 'に', 'な', 'ね'], correctAnswer: 'に' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "nu"?', options: ['ぬ', 'ね', 'の', 'に'], correctAnswer: 'ぬ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ne"?', options: ['ね', 'ぬ', 'な', 'の'], correctAnswer: 'ね' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "no"?', options: ['ぬ', 'ね', 'の', 'な'], correctAnswer: 'の' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ha"?', options: ['ほ', 'は', 'へ', 'ひ'], correctAnswer: 'は' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "hi"?', options: ['ひ', 'へ', 'ほ', 'は'], correctAnswer: 'ひ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "fu"?', options: ['ふ', 'ひ', 'へ', 'は'], correctAnswer: 'ふ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "he"?', options: ['ほ', 'へ', 'ひ', 'ふ'], correctAnswer: 'へ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ho"?', options: ['ほ', 'ひ', 'ふ', 'へ'], correctAnswer: 'ほ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ma"?', options: ['ま', 'み', 'む', 'め'], correctAnswer: 'ま' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "mi"?', options: ['む', 'み', 'ま', 'も'], correctAnswer: 'み' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "mu"?', options: ['め', 'ま', 'む', 'み'], correctAnswer: 'む' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "me"?', options: ['ま', 'め', 'む', 'み'], correctAnswer: 'め' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ya"?', options: ['よ', 'ゆ', 'や', 'え'], correctAnswer: 'や' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "yo"?', options: ['ゆ', 'よ', 'や', 'う'], correctAnswer: 'よ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ra"?', options: ['ら', 'り', 'る', 'れ'], correctAnswer: 'ら' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ri"?', options: ['る', 'れ', 'り', 'ら'], correctAnswer: 'り' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ru"?', options: ['れ', 'る', 'ら', 'ろ'], correctAnswer: 'る' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "re"?', options: ['ろ', 'ら', 'れ', 'る'], correctAnswer: 'れ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "ro"?', options: ['れ', 'ろ', 'り', 'る'], correctAnswer: 'ろ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "wa"?', options: ['わ', 'を', 'う', 'え'], correctAnswer: 'わ' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "wo"?', options: ['を', 'わ', 'う', 'え'], correctAnswer: 'を' },
  { question: 'What is the hiragana for "n"?', options: ['ん', 'な', 'ぬ', 'の'], correctAnswer: 'ん' },
];

export default hiragana;